this problem has given
us a variable favorites referencing a
nested array
the problem instructions tell us to use
the arrayflatten method
to flatten this nested array so that
it's a one-dimensional array
we're going to assign the new flattened
array
to a variable named flat favorites and
print its values so we can see it
so we'll initialize the flat favorites
variable
and we're going to assign it to the
return value of calling the arrayflatten
method
on our favorites array
let's output this new one-dimensional
array
flat favorites
and you can see that it's no longer a
nested array
and looks just like our expected output
one thing to note is that if we also
output the value of
favorites after calling the flattened
method on it
favorites is still a two-dimensional
array
and that's because the flattened method
is non-destructive
it returns a new flat array
if we want to flatten the original array
destructively
we can use the destructive flatten and
this destructive flattened method has a
bang operator at the end
now if we print flat favorites and
favorites our original nested array
they appear the same and that's because
when we used the destructive flatten we
mutated the original array